(Raj:)- That's heavy.
- Damn right, it's heavy.
It's my mother's meatloaf.
(Howard:)It's been testing toilets for generations.
(Sheldon:)I must say, Howard...
(Sheldon:)...I think a detailed letter to MIT
describing your current circumstances...
(Sheldon:)...might entitle you to a refund
on your Master's degree.
(Howard:)Okay, simulated zero-gravity human waste
disposal test with meatloaf analog.
(Howard:)In three, two, one.
(Sheldon:)Fascinating.
(Raj:)What do you think the problem is?
(Howard:)Not enough bread crumbs.
- Hey, Stuart, I need to talk to you.
- Sure, what's up?
I think I gave you some bad advice
about Penny and I want to apologize.
(Stuart:)No, your advice was great.